So now let's have a look at guardreels.
So guardreels are way for you to filter things based on your requirements to have a more
responsible AI.
So let's create a guardreel and see the options we have.
So this is my demo guardreel.
And we have here a message for blood prone.
So in case the prompt is blocked, what do you want to return to your user here?
It's going to be, sorry, the model cannot answer this question.
And this could apply as well the same message for responses or you can customize it.
Let's look on next.
And now we have options to configure a lot of things.
So we could configure content filters, denied topics, word filters, sensitive information
filters, and add contextual ground shaking.
So a lot of different options.
So let's configure one of them just so we understand how it works.
But and look at the other categories.
So here, for example, let's filter harmful categories.
So here, for example, we have a filter strength to increase the likelihood of filtering
harmful content in a given category.
So for example, no hate, no insults, no sexual, no violence, and no misconduct.
Let's click on next.
What topics do we want to deny?
So here I'm going to have call it recipes.
And the definition of a topic is what you want the foundation model to understand what
the topic is.
Let's say, for example, the topic is food recipes are instructions on how to cook specific
dishes.
And we can also add simple phrases if we really wanted to allow the AI to understand the
type of prompts we're trying to block.
But no need for us.
So let's confirm this.
So we have recipes and then click on next.
So do we want to have profanity filter, for example, if someone is using profane words?
Are the custom words and phrases to be blocked?
So you can upload them directly.
And then do you want to remove any type of personally identifiable information, PI?
So you can say, yes, I want to add a new PI, and for example, remove any type of email.
So we'll say mask and to remove any type of email.
And then rig experiment, so any type of information that follows a specific pattern should
be removed as well.
And then we have contextual grounding.
So this is to make sure that you reduce the hallucinations.
So when the model thinks that it's saying something, it takes its true, but it's actually
not true.
So I won't go into the settings here, but it's called grounding and relevance.
So let's create it and create this guard rail.
So now the guard rail is created and we can test it so we can select the model.
For example, let's choose enthropic and sonet.
And then we say here, please suggest me something to cook tonight.
I love engine food.
And let's click on run.
And here, as you can see, it's a block topic because we said no food recipes.
And the answer we get is sorry.
The model cannot answer this question.
Please, let's test it on the get time.
So please draft an email for me, include my email, Stefan@example.com.
And also include the other person's email, John@example.com, make sure we discuss important
topics for our next business meeting.
So let's click on run.
And now we are prompting the model to draft us an actual email.
This is great, but what I expect is for my emails to be masked because this is actual
information.
So as you can see here, the model response included a two Stefan@example.com and CC
John@example.com with the relevant email.
So here it discusses a lot of things.
This is great.
But the final response has been going through the guard rail.
And as you can see, the email has been masked because we, this was personally identifiable
information.
But the rest is here.
So this is great.
We've seen how this guard rail works.
And this was a good demo.
And I just want to show you another way to test the guard rail.
So if you go into text and choose, for example, again, we're going to choose anthropics
on it, apply it on the bottom here, we can choose a guard rail and apply the demo guard
rail.
And actually, you can apply many guard rails at a time if you wanted to stack them up.
So let's see for this lecture.
I hope you liked it.
You can leave this guard rail on this level and you cost you any money.
And I will see you in the next lecture.